question_data = [
    {"response_code":0,"results":[{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"Several characters in &quot;Super Mario 64&quot; blink their eyes, including Mario himself.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"In Team Fortress 2, being disguised as a scout or medic results in a speed boost.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"In Splatoon, the Squid Sisters are named Tako and Yaki.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"Hidden in the files for &quot;Mario Kart Arcade GP&quot; is a picture of the Beslan school hostage crisis.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"In career mode of &quot;Need for Speed: Underground 2&quot;, the first car the player can drive is the BMW M3 GTR.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"In Monster Hunter Generations, guild style is a type of hunting style.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"&quot;Return to Castle Wolfenstein&quot; was the only game of the Wolfenstein series where you don&#039;t play as William &quot;B.J.&quot; Blazkowicz.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"Big the Cat is a playable character in &quot;Sonic Generations&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"The names of Roxas&#039;s Keyblades in Kingdom Hearts are &quot;Oathkeeper&quot; and &quot;Oblivion&quot;.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"Codemasters is the developer of the Gran Turismo series.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"In &quot;Super Mario World&quot;, the rhino mini-boss, Reznor, is named after the lead singer of the band &quot;Nine Inch Nails&quot;.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"In &quot;Sonic Adventure&quot;, you are able to transform into Super Sonic at will after completing the main story.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"Pac-Man was invented by the designer Toru Iwatani while he was eating pizza.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"The game &quot;Jetpack Joyride&quot; was created by &quot;Redbrick Studios&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"In Sonic the Hedgehog universe, Tails&#039; real name is Miles Prower.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"In the game &quot;Subnautica&quot;, a &quot;Spadefish&quot; will attack you.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"The PlayStation was originally a joint project between Sega and Sony that was a Sega Genesis with a disc drive.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"&quot;Metal Gear Solid 3: Snake Eater&quot; was released in 2004.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"Tony Hawk&#039;s extreme sports videogames revolve around performing professional BMX tricks.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"The Ace Attorney trilogy was suppose to end with &quot;Phoenix Wright: Ace Attorney &minus; Trials and Tribulations&quot; as its final game.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]}]}